Molly hockey here your favorite Snapchat
life coach Awakening the inspiration
within for free because CU I'm not I
can't I'm not allowed to charge because
I'm not certified but today we turn to
civil rights dude MCAT mandhi best known
for his inspirational quotes be the
change you wish to see in the world he's
huge on Instagram like the fat Jewish
what kind of change do I want to see in
the world well for me I go straight to
my chin in high school they used to call
me Molly the chin hockey and Molly Leno
and and stupid Molly hockey uh the girl
that sh her pants in seventh grade PE
and um Molly sucks so stuff like that
it's not anymore though cuz here we
go I'm here with Dr Jensen doc I'm full
of self-love and I love most of my face
but I've always wanted to change my chin
what do you think well it's not a very
common procedure and the recovery time
is terribly long but I can say that the
results will be not bad bad great let's
do it
what okay uh do you have any objections
to doing this in Mexico got a couple hey
guys today's the big day the bandages
are coming off and we're going to
unleash the beauty
monster help me do you think people can
understand what I'm
saying I hope they put my MERS back
in
w wow now that's the change I want to
see you look good it's still hurts when
I
smile